credibility.com 2018-12-30

# Dun & Bradstreet Privacy Notice - D&B

What information we collect

Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixel Tags, and GIFs

### Dun & Bradstreet Privacy Notice

Dun & Bradstreet is the world’s leading source of business information and insight.  Since 1841, Dun & Bradstreet has collected information about businesses to deliver products and services that assist our customers in making critical commercial decisions.  Our global business database contains more than 300 million business records. Some of the information in the business records may be classified as personal information under various laws such as information relating to an individual (e.g. a sole trader, a partnership, a company director, a beneficial owner, a trustee, a professional contact.)

This privacy notice explains how we collect, share and protect business information. 

Back to Top

### Applicability - Legal Entities and Websites

This Privacy Notice does not apply to Dun & Bradstreet companies based in the European Union, or when any Dun & Bradstreet company processes data relating to residents of the European Union. In such cases please see the UK Privacy Notice found at <https://www.dnb.co.uk/utility-pages/privacy-policy.html>. This Privacy Notice also covers transfers of data relating to residents of the European Union to the United States pursuant to Dun &Bradstreet’s Privacy Shield certification.

This Privacy Notice applies ** ** to the following Dun & Bradstreet legal entities: Dun & Bradstreet, Inc., Dun & Bradstreet NetProspex, Inc. ("NPX"); Avention, Inc.; Hoover’s Inc.; Dun & Bradstreet Emerging Businesses ("DBEB"). NPX, Avention, and Hoover’s provide Sales and Marketing solutions.  DBEB provides business credit information. Market Data Retrieval (MDR), a part of Dun and Bradstreet Inc., is a provider of marketing information and services for the K-12, higher education, library, early childhood, and related education market.  These entities and lines of business will be referred to collectively as “Dun & Bradstreet” in this notice.

This policy covers the following Dun & Bradstreet websites:  [dnb.com](https://www.dnb.com/), [DandB.com](https://www.dandb.com/index.html), [accesstocapital.com](http://accesstocapital.com/), [products.dandb.com](https://www.dandb.com/index.html), [dandbeducation.com](http://dandbeducation.com/), [companyupdate.com](https://www.dandb.com/product/companyupdate/companyupdateLogin?execution=e1s1), [EdAhead.org](http://edahead.org/), [education.dandb.com](http://education.dandb.com/), [CreditSignal.com](https://www.creditsignal.com/), [businesscredit.dnb.com](https://businesscredit.dnb.com/), [creditreports.dnb.com](https://businesscredit.dnb.com/), [b2b.dnb.com](https://b2b.dnb.com/), [dnb.com/mktsem/microsite-business-credit-solutions.html](https://www.dnb.com/mktsem/microsite-business-credit-solutions.html), [cart.dnb.com](http://cart.dnb.com/), [hoovers.com](http://www.hoovers.com/); [sales.hoovers.com](https://www.dnb.com/), [yourhoovers.com](http://yourhoovers.com/), and [products.hoovers.com](http://www.hoovers.com/), mdreducation.com, [ednetconference.com](http://ednetconference.com/).

These sites may provide links to other U.S. Dun & Bradstreet websites, non-U.S. Dun & Bradstreet websites and non-Dun & Bradstreet websites that may have different privacy notices. We encourage you to carefully read the online privacy notices of these other websites to ensure that you understand their practices and the relevant distinctions.

Back to Top

### What information we collect

_Products and Services_

Dun & Bradstreet collects information on businesses and business professionals. We collect information offline from business owners and principals, from businesses' creditors, vendors, third parties and suppliers, and from public records such as business registrations, Uniform Commercial Code filings and bankruptcy filings. MDR collects information on educational institutions and professionals.  Dun & Bradstreet has a right to publish information on businesses that may be a factor in our customers’ decision making involving credit, insurance, marketing and other activities.  The business information that we collect includes the following:

Company and business professional information, including business contact information such as name, title, address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address, domain names, and trade associations

Detailed company profiles and statistics, including number of employees;

Background information regarding company management, such as beneficial ownership/persons of significant control, the educational and career histories of company principals;

Company operational histories, including territories, subsidiaries, affiliates, and lines of business;

Detailed trade and business credit information, including payment histories and patterns;

Summary business information regarding profitability, debts, assets, net worth, and business relationships;

Business compliance information from public source government and professional records, media and business publications

Educational institutional profiles and statistics, including educational subject matter specialties and number of employees

Background information regarding educational institutional management, such as the educational and career histories of school deans and principals

IP addresses, geolocation, comments on social media is collected and aggregated and used to analyze trends regarding Dun & Bradstreet products and services.

Credit/debit card information in order to process certain customer payments.

**Personal Information You Provide Through Websites** : includes name, address, telephone number, social media handle, email address, employer, job title. We collect personal information from website visitors and when you purchase products and services through our website, apply for Dun & Bradstreet D-U-N-S® Number; subscribe to email newsletters and alerts, fill out a form to request additional information; participate in Community Forums; enter a contest; fill out a survey; access video content; receive free incentives.

PLEASE NOTE: Your registration information and/or any information collected by D&B when you visit websites is not included in the D&B professional business contacts database.  

**Personal Information Collected In The Scope Of Marketing Activities** : Your personal information may be collected when you enter contests and participate in other promotions; when we conduct webinars, demand generation campaigns, when we disseminate white papers, e-books or similar content, when you click on landing pages, in the course of Pay-Per-Click campaigns, and similar events and methods.

When you sign up to participate in D&B hosted blogs, tutorials, and social media, we will collect personally identifiable information in order to establish your profile. You may choose to make public certain individual profile elements, in which case that information will be available to visitors and possibly to other users of the Internet. Any information that you submit and post may likewise be available to website visitors and viewable to anyone online. Your blog postings will be associated with your username and your voluntarily created public profile. Violation of our Terms of Use agreement may result in the removal of your post(s) and/or the termination of your membership.

**Information Collected Automatically Through Computer Tracking** : We also collect information about website visitors such as IP address, browser type, or operating system, areas of the website visited and the website from which a visitor came. We collect and analyze this information for the continued improvement of the Products, Websites, and our business. We routinely use this web log information to administer and improve our website.  While some of this information may be traceable to an individual, we only seek to identify individuals (i) whom we believe are using our website for improper purposes, (ii) when necessary to assist them with their user experience, (iii) or to otherwise use the information as described in this policy.

Dun & Bradstreet analyzes IP addresses of visitors to our websites and match business information from our various databases and received from third parties against the IP addresses to learn more about what types of businesses are visiting our websites and the browsing preferences of such businesses on our websites. We use the information derived from these analytical activities, which may be combined with non-personally identifiable behavioral information received from third parties, to better model and refine our general marketing activities and may, from time to time and to the extent permitted by law, directly market our products and services to these businesses based on the information we have learned about their browsing activities while on our websites.  In addition, Hoover’s analyzes IP addresses from Hoover’s products users to match business information from our various databases and received from third parties against users’ IP addresses for our internal analytical purposes which helps us to increase the accuracy of the information in our various business information databases.

**Mobile Devices: _  _**To provide location-based services on the mobile-optimized versions of products, we may collect and use precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your mobile device or computer. Where available, location-based services may use GPS, Bluetooth, and your IP Address, along with crowd-sourced Wi-Fi hotspot and cell tower locations, and other technologies to determine your device’s approximate location. Location-based services, such as the mapping features, require collection of your location for the feature to work. You may withdraw consent to its collection, use, transmission, processing and maintenance of location data at any time by not using the products that use location-based features or by turning off Location Services settings (as applicable) on your device and computer.)

Dun & Bradstreet does not respond to Do Not Track Signals.

### How Do We Use and Share Information?

Dun & Bradstreet uses the information that we collect to operate our websites, offer customers a variety of business information products and services for use in making business credit, risk management, supplier, and marketing decisions, and to carry out transactions that you request or authorize. Dun & Bradstreet also licenses professional business contact information to authorized resellers and third party businesses for marketing and data management purposes.

We may use your professional business contact information to match it with other public and private sources in order to create anonymous segments of information (this is non-personally identifying information, such as demographic, behavioral and technical information, extracted from the underlying Data) for use by Dun & Bradstreet and/or third parties to target advertising messages to you on third party sites and services. Such segments do not reveal or contain your personal information. You may opt-out from certain targeting advertising by following the instructions in the section below entitled "Third Party Advertisers". Dun & Bradstreet follows the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as administered by the Digital Advertising Alliance. Visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> to exercise your option to opt-out of targeted ads provided by certain listed companies.

Hoover's maintains a separate professional contacts directory in which your company and individual business contact information may be listed. Hoover's licenses business and professional contact information to authorized resellers and third party businesses for marketing purposes. Aggregated website visitor data may be used to determine usage patterns or interests of visitors to the website and users of our products, or for purposes related to technical support or security of the website, products and computer systems. Usage information, such as number of reports, types of reports and functions accessed by a particular UserID, may be tracked within the products. We do this to monitor authorized usage of the products, respond to questions from the user, for market research, and to improve the design and functionality of the products. We may also aggregate corporate or industry information accessed by all of our customers. We do this in order to appreciate the types of companies and industries for which our customers require information, which in turn improves the quality of the products. We do not correlate the accessed corporate or industry information to a specific user or to a particular organization.

Dun & Bradstreet shares information with third party service providers, such as credit card processors, auditors, attorneys, consultants, live help/chat providers and contractors, in order to support Dun & Bradstreet's Internet websites and business operations. Dun & Bradstreet contractually requires that these recipients only use the information for the intended purpose of the disclosure and that they destroy or return the information when it is no longer needed. We may also disclose the information as required or appropriate in order to protect our website, business operations or legal rights, or in connection with a sale or merger involving Dun & Bradstreet assets or businesses.

From time to time, Dun & Bradstreet compiles online and offline transaction and registration information for internal analyses, such as market research, quality assurance, customer experience, and operational benchmarking initiatives.

When necessary or appropriate, we may disclose information in response to a court order, subpoena, law enforcement proceeding, regulatory inquiry or when otherwise legally required. Also, be advised that Dun & Bradstreet sometimes receives requests (e.g., court order, subpoena, law enforcement proceeding,) for personal information from public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. In responding those requests D&B's response will be limited (a) to the extent necessary to meet national security, public interest, or law enforcement requirements or (b) by statute, government regulation or case law that creates conflicting obligations or explicit authorizations.

### Collection of Sensitive Personally Identifiable Information

Dun & Bradstreet may collect sensitive personally identifiable information ("SPI") associated with certain customers or customers' clients, such as individuals' Social Security Numbers and dates of birth, in order to provide certain product and service offerings.  We will only collect this SPI if it is necessary to fulfill certain product orders and only when voluntarily provided by the customer.  We will only use it for the limited, permissible purpose for which it is collected and we will take commercially reasonable steps to adequately secure the information. We may also share this SPI with trusted third parties for the limited, permissible purpose of fulfilling the associated product orders.

Back to Top

### Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixel Tags, and GIFs

_What are Cookies, Flash Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixel Tags and GIFs and how are they used?_  

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer's hard drive and that often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that website's computer asks your computer for permission to store this text file in a section of your hard drive that is specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it. Your browser will only permit a website to access the cookies that it has previously sent to you and not the cookies sent to you by other websites

We use cookies to store login or other information on your computer, which serves to improve our website functionality and tailor our services to your preferences and interests. Other uses include preventing, detecting and investigating potentially prohibited or illegal activities, including enforcing our Terms of Use agreement. For certain services, we offer users the ability to store a user ID or password within a cookie so that they do not need to re-enter it when they subsequently return to our website. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our website and to assess which parts of the site are most popular. This information helps us to constantly improve our website and better serve our customers and some of our cookies may be tied to personally identifiable information. We do not store credit/debit card numbers in cookies.

For new visitors, we use first party cookies or Web beacons (placed on your browser by Dun & Bradstreet) to collect limited data, such as the date, time, and areas of our website that are visited, as well as the website from which the new visitor came. We may use IP addresses to derive certain other information concerning businesses visiting our websites as described in this policy, but we do not analyze this information in a way which would reveal the identity of the individual browsing our websites. When you select one of our products or services, register for a newsletter or e-mail alert, fill out an online form, or complete a survey, we may try to identify your browser and we may combine information from cookies, Web beacons, code and other information collected online with other data that we maintain about you. By improving the features, marketing, and content of our website and by making your online experience more convenient and meaningful, we are able to better serve our customers' needs.

We may use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how Data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).

A Web beacon is a graphic image, such as a pixel tag or clear GIF, which is placed on a Web page or in an e-mail message to monitor user activity, such as whether the Web page or e-mail message is accessed or clicked. They are often invisible because they are very small in size. They are also used on many Web pages for alignment purposes.

We sometimes use Web beacons to provide an independent accounting of how many people visit our website or to gather statistics about browser usage on our website. Some of our Web pages and HTML-formatted e-mail newsletters use Web beacons in conjunction with cookies. It is difficult for you to limit the use of Web beacons because there is no easy way to distinguish their use from alignment and other purposes. Web beacons may also be loaded from a different Web server than the rest of the page.

Some of our e-mails may also contain pixels or code to gather information regarding e-mail behavior and analytics. We may share this encrypted information with third parties for e-mail analytics purposes.

Some of our business partners, such as third party advertisers, use cookies that originate from their websites. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. For more information, please see the "Third Party Advertisers" section below.

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. In the course of serving advertisements, our third party advertisers and partners may place or recognize a unique third party cookie on your browser. These companies may use information about your visits to Dun & Bradstreet’s and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. These third party partners monitor how guests use our website and determine which of our online features they prefer. We may report information to our partners about our customers and the products and services they order, as well as aggregated, non-identifiable information about our guests' use of our website. For more information, please see the "Third Party Advertisers" section below.

We use third party advertising companies to serve our Internet ad banners on our website and other websites on which we advertise The use of third party cookies and other tracking technologies is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access to or control of any third party tracking technologies. Third party advertisers may also use a third party analytics provider to place third party cookies on your browser in order to collect anonymous and aggregated session Data, such as the ads that are viewed. If you view a Web page where our ads appear, the advertising company may place a cookie on your computer or use a Web beacon to access a cookie that they previously placed on your computer. These companies do not collect information that can personally identify you, but they may use information about your visits to our website and other websites to measure the effectiveness of ads. We do not disclose any personally identifiable information to these companies. We share aggregate website usage information with third party advertisers and partners for the purpose of effectively targeting our online advertisements. Unless you are previously notified, these advertising companies do not link any online behavior or cookies with other information that can be used to personally identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address, when working with Dun & Bradstreet.

These third party advertising networks also track visitors' online usage and behavior patterns. These companies may use information about your visits to Dun & Bradstreet and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The result of these efforts is the creation of an online profile that attempts to predict individual user interests, preferences and purchasing habits. The third party advertising networks then accordingly customize the advertising content served to users when visiting other websites.

_What are your choices regarding Cookies_  

Most Internet browsers allow users to decide whether to accept cookies and how long to keep them on their hard drive. You may reset your browser to refuse cookies and still use our website, although website access and functionality may be slower and less convenient.

In regard to Third Party Advertisers, the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) is a self-regulatory cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies. The NAI provides educational content and opt-out tools to help Internet users learn about and address online behavioral marketing practices. Through the NAI's online options, you may opt out of particular NAI network members' behavioral advertising programs or you may opt out of all NAI network members' programs. Opting out will prevent the given network from which you opted out from using your Web preferences and usage patterns to deliver targeted online ads. The NAI opt-out only works with participating third party advertising networks that use cookies and Web beacons to execute their advertising initiatives. If you would like additional information about online behavioral marketing and your options regarding these standard Internet practices, please visit the [NAI website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

### You Have Choices

Dun & Bradstreet respects your privacy preferences and offers the following ways through which you may control how we contact you and disclose your information.

_Dun & Bradstreet E-mail Marketing_

To opt out of receiving Dun & Bradstreet promotional e-mails, newsletters, and updates about new Dun & Bradstreet features, products and services:

You can manage your notifications and communications at the Communications Preference Center or you may follow the unsubscribe instructions in any of our promotional emails.  You can also reach Customer Service at 1-800-234-3867 or send an email to [custservprivacy@dnb.com](mailto:custservprivacy@dnb.com). 

You may change your preferences at any time.

Please note that we may continue to send you transactional or service-related e-mails despite your desire to not receive promotional or marketing e-mail messages.  Also please note that if you elect to opt-out of receiving promotional e-mails from one of our websites, you may continue to receive promotional emails from our other websites. 

_Dun & Bradstreet Telemarketing, Texting or Calling_  

To no longer receive telemarketing calls from us or seek to clearly inform Dun & Bradstreet of a desire to revoke consent provided in the below paragraph, you may do this by:

Calling Dun & Bradstreet Customer at 1-800-234-3867

Clicking on the Dun & Bradstreet Communications Preference link https://www.dnb.com/utility-pages/communication-preferences.html

By providing your phone number to Dun & Bradstreet, you expressly consented and authorized Dun & Bradstreet to contact you in any lawful manner, including the use of automatic and/or computerized dialing systems, text messages and pre-recorded message and call technologies for any lawful purpose, including marketing Dun & Bradstreet products and third party services. You expressly consent to be contacted through such means at the telephone numbers (including mobile or wireless numbers) you provide to Dun & Bradstreet. You represent and warrant that any mobile or wireless telephone number you provide belongs to you and is associated with a mobile device in your possession. You will notify Dun & Bradstreet if your mobile or wireless telephone number changes. Consent is not a requirement of purchase. Should you have any questions about which addresses, telephone numbers or email addresses you provided to Dun & Bradstreet for the above, please review your account information in your product dashboard or please call Dun & Bradstreet at 1-800-234-3867.

We may continue to call you for transactional or service-related purposes despite your desire to not receive telemarketing calls.

_Dun & Bradstreet Direct Mail Marketing_  

To be placed on our company's internal Do Not Mail list should you no longer wish to receive marketing or promotional mailers you may do so by contacting: Dun & Bradstreet Customer Service at 1-800-234-3867 or clicking on the Dun & Bradstreet Communications Preference link: <https://www.dnb.com/utility-pages/communication-preferences.html>

You may change your preferences at any time.

We may continue to send you transactional or service-related correspondence despite your desire to not receive marketing mailers.

Individuals whose contact information is in our professional contacts database may request to be excluded from the professional contacts database, by calling Dun & Bradstreet at 800-234-3867 or emailing  [custservprivacy@dnb.com](mailto:custservprivacy@dnb.com)

While we may remove your individual business contact information from our professional contacts database, please be aware that we will continue to provide your company's or educational institution’s contact information in our Business Information and Educational Institutional Reports and other products and services. Note that if your professional contact information is in a different third party's marketing directory, you will need to request removal with such third party directly.

### Access, Correction, and Deletion

To help ensure data quality and accuracy, Dun & Bradstreet provides businesses organizations and business professionals with access to their business information within the D&B databases and with an opportunity to review such information, correct verified inaccuracies, or delete any personal information within such business information if required by law. Authorized business representatives may request a complimentary copy of their company's business report.

To obtain a copy of your company’s business report or your information or, to correct or update your information:

Dun & Bradstreet Customer Service at 1-800-234-3867 or send an email to  _[custservprivacy@dnb.com](mailto:custservprivacy@dnb.com)_

Hoovers/Avention: Customer Support at 1-800-486-8666 or by sending an e-mail to  _[customersupport@hoovers.com](mailto:customersupport@hoovers.com)_

When a business owner or principal contacts Dun & Bradstreet about a potential data error, we promptly investigate the issue, confirm the information in question, correct verified inaccuracies or delete any personal information within such business information if required by law, and respond to the original inquiry. In such a case, we may apply a "stop distribution" order regarding the relevant business report, as well as ancillary products that may be affected by the verified inaccuracy, until the matter is properly resolved. When the investigation is complete, we will also send a correction or deletion notice to businesses or others whom we know to have received the inaccurate data, as appropriate. However, some third parties and third party sites may continue to display inaccurate Data until their databases and display of data are refreshed in accordance with their update schedules.

### Data Security

Dun & Bradstreet maintains commercially reasonable security measures to protect personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure and that are consistent with our business operations and generally accepted industry standards. These measures include the implementation of technical, physical and administrative security safeguards. Dun & Bradstreet requires employees to complete privacy and security training.  Dun & Bradstreet also implements a third party service provider due diligence program to ensure that our vendors likewise employ adequate data collection, processing, transfer, management and security measures in carrying out their services on our behalf.

We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us and you agree that you provide this information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive information from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems. Dun & Bradstreet has established policies and procedures for securely managing information and protecting Data against unauthorized access and we continually assess our data privacy, information management and data security practices. We do this in the following ways:

Establishing policies and procedures for securely managing information;

Limiting employee access to sensitive information;

Protecting against unauthorized access to customer data by using data encryption, authentication and virus detection technology, as required;

Requiring service providers with whom we do business to comply with relevant data privacy legal and regulatory requirements;

Monitoring our websites through recognized online privacy and security organizations;

Conducting background checks on employees and providing Data Privacy training to our team members;

Continually assessing our data privacy, information management and data security practices.

### Data Retention

Dun & Bradstreet will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact Dun & Bradstreet Customer Service at 1-800-234-3867 or [custservprivacy@dnb.com](mailto:custservprivacy@dnb.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Children

Dun & Bradstreet websites, products and services are for business purposes only. They are not targeted, intended or expected to be of use to children. User provided contributions of content or contact information regarding or about children are expressly prohibited.

### Changes To Data Privacy Practices

If we make material changes to our data privacy practices, this policy will be updated and posted on our website in order to keep you informed of how we collect, use, manage, disclose, and protect information. The policy effective date will be updated accordingly.

### Your Use of Our Website is Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our collection, use, management, retention, and disclosure of your information as described in this policy.

### Sale of Assets

In the event that Dun & Bradstreet is purchased or sells parts or all of the business, the information collected will be considered an asset that can be transferred.

### Transfers of Personal Information from the EU/EEA and Switzerland to the US - Privacy Shield

Dun & Bradstreet and its legal entities comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU or Swiss individuals received pursuant to Privacy Shield, Dun & Bradstreet is potentially liable. Dun & Bradstreet has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

Dun & Bradstreet is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

### Other Transfer Mechanisms

Dun & Bradstreet also complies with EU/EEA to US cross border transfer requirements by entering into standard contractual clauses or using other mechanisms available under the EU Data protection laws. We also use data transfer agreements or other approved mechanisms for global transfers of personal information.

### Dispute Resolution

This dispute resolution program covers both offline Data collection (e.g. personal information collected through our call centers or via postal mail) and online Data collection (e.g. personal information collected via the Internet). If you are a citizen of the EU and you have any complaints regarding our compliance with relevant aspects of the Data transfer laws and regulations surrounding Data transfers from the EU you should contact us at: _[EUDPO@dnb.com](mailto:eudpo@dnb.com)_ or _[customerhelp@dnb.co.uk](mailto:eudpo@dnb.com)_.

If you are not a citizen of the EU and you have a question or concern regarding Dun & Bradstreet's data privacy practices, please contact the Chief Privacy Officer at _[privacyofficer@dnb.com](mailto:privacyofficer@dnb.com)_ or call the Customer Service center at 1-800-234-3867 or send an email to& _[custservprivacy@dnb.com](mailto:custservprivacy@dnb.com)_. We will do our best to resolve any complaints or issues as quickly as possible.

If we cannot resolve your complaints, you may have rights to independent dispute resolution or arbitration under certain circumstances as described below in the sections titled “Independent Dispute Resolution” and “Arbitration.”

### Independent Dispute Resolution

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, you may invoke binding arbitration under certain circumstances. Please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at  _<https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>_ , and the section below titled “Arbitration.”

### Arbitration

__In accordance with the Privacy Shield, individuals may invoke binding arbitration as a final recourse for claims that a Privacy Shield organization has violated its obligations under the Principles and the claim is not fully resolved by other Privacy Shield recourse mechanisms. The arbitration will be implemented in accordance with the rules established under the Privacy Shield.

### California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please see the Access and Correction section above for contact information.

### Contact

For more information regarding this Privacy Notice, you can contact:

Privacy Officer  
Dun & Bradstreet, Inc.  
103 JFK Parkway  
Short Hills, NJ 07078  

If you are an EU citizen and have questions regarding your personal information or about Dun & Bradstreet's EU Privacy Policy, you can contact: 

EU Data Protection Officer at [EUDPO@dnb.com](mailto:EU%20Data%20Protection%20Officer%20at%20EUDPO@dnb.com)

### Effective Date:

Effective Date of this Privacy Notice: October 8, 2018

This update to the Privacy Notice was done to update our notices regarding access, correction, and deletion of certain information, as well as clarify our notices regarding dispute resolution and arbitration.

Previous update to this Privacy Notice was dated September 17, 2018.
